Guide to the The Class Notes records, 1990-2017.
Class Notes records, The
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The Class Notes records 1990-2017
37-6-4269
Class Notes
25 gigabytes.; 0.1 cubic feet.
{**Comma Separated List Of Material Formats,End With Period**.}
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Music, photos, CDs, videos, sheet music arrangements, membership lists, history and files relating to the administration and performances of the Class Notes.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Class Notes are a co-ed a cappella group founded in 1983 that performs a varied repertoire of contemporary Pop, R&B, Rock and Hip-hop songs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Music, photos, CDs, videos, sheet music arrangements, membership lists, history and files relating to the administration and performances of the Class Notes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Class Notes; Cornell University -- Students.
Subjects:
A cappella; Choral societies.; Choirs.; Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices), Unaccompanied.; Music -- Societies, etc.; Music -- Performance.; Singers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Business Card, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Early business card created by original Class Notes members
- Personal from Sun, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Personal posted in Cornell Daily Sun in Spring 1984
- Cornell Jamboree I Program, 1984-11-30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  First Jamboree program featuring the 5 existing a cappella groups in 1984
- 3 Letters from David Lefkowitz, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  3 Letters from David Lefkowitz, group founder, to current group members
- Letter from Tina Johnson, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Letter from Tina, group founder, to current group members
- Class Notes Attendance Policy, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Attendance policy of group at that time
- Concert Schedule, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  List of concerts, Spring 1984
- Concert Schedule, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  List of concerts, Fall 1984
- Group Phone List, 1984-11-10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Contact Info and song list for Fall 1984
- Sheet Music, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Sheet music from the group's early years
- 2012 ICCA Quarterfinals Certificate, 2012-02-18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Quarterfinal Champion Certificate from the Varsity Vocals International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella
- ICCA Quarterfinals Judge Sheet 2012, 2012-02-18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Judge sheet from 2012 ICCA Quarterfinals for Class Notes, Cornell U
- ICCA Semifinals Judge Sheet 2012, 2012-03-24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Judge sheet from 2012 ICCA Semifinals for Class Notes, Rutgers U
- Cuttin' Class VI Program, 1989-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Original Program used for concert
- Cornell Jamboree VI Program, 1990-02-24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cuttin' Class V Program, 1989-04-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cornell Jamboree V Program, 1988-10-08 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cuttin' Class IV Program, 1987-11-21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cornell Jamboree IV Program, 1988-02-19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cuttin' Class XX Program, 2004-02-24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Itinerary for Cuttin' Class XX, 2004-02-24 (Box 1)
  Itinarary for alumni who were participating in Cuttin' Class XX
- Class Notes Anniversary Stickers, 2004-02 (Box 1)
  Stickers made for use with activities related to Cuttin' Class XX and the Class Notes' 20th Anniversary Celebration
- Cuttin' Class XX Mini-Flyer, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  Mini-flyer announcing Cuttin' Class XX
- Class Notes Stickers, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  Stickers made with a rubber stamp in the late 1980s. Sticker is of one of the earliest Class Notes logos.
- Class Notes Brochure, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  Brochure for group created around 1986-1987 and used in the late 80s. Photos are of group around Fall 1986.